{
    "subject": "resource/Gallant_Journey",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_set_in_the_1890s",
    "human_readable": "The Gallant Journey is set in the 1890s.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9607057571411133,
            "question": "How might the setting of the 1890s influence the characters and plot of The Gallant Journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8163366317749023,
            "question": "How might the political climate of the 1890s affect the story of The Gallant Journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7936162352561951,
            "question": "In what historical period is The Gallant Journey set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522879242897034,
            "question": "What decade does The Gallant Journey take place in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5231488943099976,
            "question": "Are there any historical events that could play a role in The Gallant Journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.367114394903183,
            "question": "What type of transportation would have been common in the 1890s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3639369010925293,
            "question": "During which years unfolds the story of The Gallant Journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3232475221157074,
            "question": "What social or technological advancements might be featured in The Gallant Journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31190919876098633,
            "question": "What was life like in the 1890s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2026081532239914,
            "question": "What fashion trends were popular during the 1890s?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Gallant Journey is set in the 1890s.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5654_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was life like in the 1890s?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5654_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What social or technological advancements might be featured in The Gallant Journey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5654_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During which years unfolds the story of The Gallant Journey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5654_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5654_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that  Gallant Journey depicts John Joseph Montgomery's life \"from his childhood through to his death in 1911.\" This indicates the film is set around the early 20th century, not the 1890s. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The film \"Gallant Journey\" is mentioned multiple times, and it's stated that principal photography took place from March 4 to June 1, 1946. This implies that the film was indeed set in the 1940s.\n* There's no mention of a specific time period (1890s) being associated with \"The Gallant Journey\".\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\nThe information provided does not support that \"The Gallant Journey\" is set in the 1890s. According to the documents, it is a biopic of John Joseph Montgomery, an early U.S. aviation pioneer, and mentions his efforts from childhood through to his death in 1911. There's no specific mention of the 1890s as the setting for the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}